Guide to the Travel brochure and map collection, [19--].
Travel brochure and map collection, [19--]
- Description: City/ Region, State
  - Tourist map: Suomi-Finland, Finland (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - The Roads: Entire, France (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Tours: Entire, France (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Taride: Entire and territories, France (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Guide: Entire, France (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Guide: Entire, France (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Map: Douce France, France (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Pamphlet: French Civilization, France (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Handbook: Avignon, France (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Practical Guide: Avignon, France (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Album: Chateau Thierry, France (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Guide Book: Cote D'Azure, France (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Detachable cards: Cote D'Azure, France (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - After the Last battle: La Pompelle Berry, France (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Post Cards: Les Baux, France (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Institute of Paris: Paris, France (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Railway Guide: Paris-Lyon, France (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Leaflet: How to travel by bus and underground like a Parisian, Paris, France (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Map: Paris, France (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Map: Paris, France (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Map: Paris, France (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Pamphlet: Musée du Louvre, France (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Michelin Map: Pyrénées, France (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Guide: Bavaria, Germany (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Map: Berlin, Germany (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Map: Berlin, Germany (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Guidebook and map: Bremerhaven, Germany (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Map and leaflet: Goslar, Germany (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - map: Kaiserslautern, Germany (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Guide: Linderhof Castle, Germany (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - map: Lübeck, Germany (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - map: Mainz, Germany (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Guide: Neuschwanstien Castle, Germany (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Durerhouse: Nuremburg, Germany (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Map and leaflets: Nürnberg, Germany (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Passion Play House: Oberammergau, Germany (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Guide: Rothenburg on the tauber, Germany (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Leaflet: Rothenburg, Hotel Eisenhut, Germany (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Map: Wiesbaden, Germany (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Map: Worms, Germany (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Guide: Happy Days in Germany (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Map: Deutschland, Germany (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Greece: Acropolis 1961 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Greece: A Visitor's Guide to Mycenae Argo-Tiryns-Nauplia and Epidaurus (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Greece: An American in Greece (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Greece: Cloistre of Kaissariani (leaflet) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Greece: map of Athens (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Greece: Athens Information (leaflet) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Guatemala: The land of enchantment and color (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Hotels/Resorts: Six Continents Club kit (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Hotels/Resorts: Intercontinental, Chicago, Illinois (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Iceland: map of entire island (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Iceland: Icelandic Airlines leaflet (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - India: A Democracy on the Move (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - India: Newest & Latest Map of Bihar State 1975 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Guide: Indonesia (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Indonesia: Bali (leaflet) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Indonesia: Balikpapan, Borneo (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Guide and map: Sumatra, Indonesia (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Guide: Tosari, Indonesia (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Muckross Abbey, Dublin, Ireland 1906 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Ireland (travel guide) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Northern Ireland (travel guide) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Gresham Hotel, Dublin, Ireland 1965 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Welcome to the Gresham Hotel (Dublin, Ireland) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Johnstown Castle Estate and Research Center, Ireland (4 miles S.W. of Wexford) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Traveller's Map of Italy 1970 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Travel in Italy 1967 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Mosaici: Piazza Armerina, Italy (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Visitor's Guide: Lucca, Italy (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Do You Know Italy? (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Florence, Italy (map) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - "Casa Guidi," Florence, Italy (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Grosseto, Italy (guide) 1938 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Lago Maggiore, Italy (photo album) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Ravenna, Italy (map) 1963 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Ravenna, Italy (map) 1965 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Rome, Italy (map) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - How to visit Rome and its environs, Italy (tour book) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Sicily, Italy (guide) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Italy (guide and map) 1955 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Italy (Michelin guide) 1961 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - The Mountains Blush: The Dolomites, Italy (guide) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - XVth Century map of Venice, Italy (copy) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Venice, Italy (map) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Ivory Coast: Zembla 1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Tokyo, Japan (map) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - How to See Tokyo, Japan (guide) 1953 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - How to See Tokyo, Japan (guide) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Welcome to Yoshicho: Tokyo, Japan (booklet) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Imperial Hotel, Tokyo, Japan (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - From the Car Window: Tokyo-Osaka, Japan (train guide) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Card packets (5), Japan (guide) 1953 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Annual Events in Japan (program) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - National Park Hakone Japan (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Grand Duché de Luxembourg (map) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Grand Duché de Luxembourg (map) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Renseignements Touristiques, Grand-Duché de Luxembourg (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Tourist Information, Grand Duchy of Luxembourg (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Plan de la Ville de Luxembourg (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Beaufort - Dillingen - Grundhof, Luxembourg (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Dianden, Luxembourg (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Diekirch, Luxembourg (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Ecternach, Luxembourg (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Larochette, Luxembourg (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Merche, Luxembourg (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Mexico (map) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Mexico (map) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Puebla, Colonial, Mexico (guide) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Mexico and Central America (map) 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Mexico and Central America (guide) 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Mexico and Central America (guide) 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Mexico: Mexico City (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Mexico: Acapulco Hotels (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Ticket in Commemoration of Visit of Tian Anmen Gate (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Middle East: Lands of the Bible Today (map) 1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Cultural Map of the Middle East 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Middle East (map) 1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Middle East: Lands of the Bible Today (map) 1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Middle East: Holy Land Excursions (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Lunar surface, Moon (map) 1969 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Bruges, Netherlands (guide) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Madurodam, Netherlands (map) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Madurodam, Netherlands (advertisement) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Reizen (borderlands), Netherlands (advertisement) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Tombeax Royaux, Netherlands (guide) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Tourist information: Netherlands (leaflet with maps) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Diamond Jubilee, Netherlands (pamphlet) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Tourist advertisement: Netherlands (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - "How much does it cost to live with the Dutch?": Netherlands (pamphlet) 1961 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Mynheer Van Schlichtenhorth and the Old Dutch Burghers: Regarding America, Netherlands 1906 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Holland Hails You: Regarding America, Netherlands 1945 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Hier is New-York (guide) 1960 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Panorama der Vereenigde Staten: Regarding America, Netherlands (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Amerika: Regarding America, Netherlands (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Netherlands and the US: Regarding America, Netherlands 1982 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - New Zealand (map guide) 1985 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Christchurch Cathedral, Christchurch, New Zealand (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Elveseter Hotel, Norway (leaflet) 1956 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Oslo, Norway (guide) 1960 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Oslo, Norway (map) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - City portrait of Oslo, Norway (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Norske folkemuseum, Norway (guide and map) 1958 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - The Oseberg find and the other Viking ship finds, Oseberg, Norway (pamphlet) 1957 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Ocean topography: Atlantic Ocean floor (map) 1968 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Ocean topography: Indian Ocean floor (map) 1967 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Ocean topography: Pacific Ocean floor (map) 1969 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Ocean topography: Indian Ocean Region (map) 1941 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Discoverers of the Pacific, Pacific + S.E Asia 1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Peoples of Mainland S.E Asia, Pacific + S.E Asia 1971 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - The Peoples of Mainland Southeast Asia (map) 1971 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Panama Canal souvenir, Panama 1914 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Panama Canal: general information, Panama 1914 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Peru: Las Mejores Vistas del Peru Series No. 23: Chanchamayo (photograph packet) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Limatamba, Peru: Souvenirs Plateria (broadsides) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Philippines: An Invitation to the Philippines (booklet) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Philippines: Where Asia Wears a Smile: Primer on the Philippines 1976 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Philippines: Where Asia Wears a Smile: Official Guidebook (guide) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Philippines: Nation's Journal (supplement of the Times-Journal [o/s]) 1978 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Russia: Leningrad (brochure) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Russia: Moscow (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Russia: Moscow (illustrated map) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Russia: Yaroslavl (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Russia: New Times (periodical) 1987 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Russia: Cruise the Passage of Peter the Great (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Russia: Russia's Imperial Treasures (leaflet) 1988 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Russia: Visit the USSR (booklet) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Russia: The Soviet Transcaucasia (booklet) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Russia: Michael Gorbachev (banner) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Prague, Czechoslovakia (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Map of Russia 1993 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Paterson's Guide: Edinburgh, Scotland 1887 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Holyroodhouse: Edinburgh, Scotland 1906 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Pitlochry, Scotland (guide) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Edinburgh: capital of Scotland (guide) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Edinburgh, Scotland (guide) 1969 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Scotland (brochure) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Clan Map of the Scottish Highlands (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Historical Map of Scotland (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Church of Scotland, Perceton & Dreghorn Parish Church Centenary (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Argyll and Bute, Scotland (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Northern Scotland, (map) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Bartholomew tartan map: Scotland (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Summer Tours in Scotland (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Johnson's Clan Histories/The Clan MacLean: Scotland (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Scotland the Brave (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Scotland in Pictures (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Maaes Howe - Scotland 1993 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Hotel Golf, Slovenia (menu) (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Guide du Pneu Michelin: Espagne 1953 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Barcelona Modernismeo, Spain (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Hotel Calderon Restaurante, Barcelona, Spain (postcard) (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Alhambra Palace, Grenada, Spain 1929 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Plan to Stay in Sunny Ceylon [Sri Lanka] (booklet) (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Northern Sweden (guide) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Skansen, Sweden (map) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Stockholm, Sweden (map) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Shopping guide to Stockholm, Sweden (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Railway map of Sweden (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Skokloster, Stockholm, Sweden (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Sweden (guide) 1954 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Bern, Switzerland (booklet) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Bern, Switzerland (map) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Bienne-Biel, Switzerland (booklet) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Come and see the Emmental, Switzerland (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Geneva, Switzerland (map) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Palais des nations, Switzerland (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Palais des nations, Switzerland (guide) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Switzerland (guide) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Innsbruck, Switzerland (map) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Innsbruck, Switzerland (map) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Jungfrau, Switzerland (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Jungfrau region, Switzerland (map) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Jungfrau excursion, Switzerland (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Luzern, Switzerland (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Mt. Pilate, Luzern, Switzerland (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Grand Hotel, Lucerne, Switzerland (leaflet + menu) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Casagrande, Lucerne, Switzerland (postcard) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - St. Gall, Switzerland (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Abbey library, St. Gall, Switzerland (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Zermatt, Switzerland (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - EAPR programme, Zurich, Switzerland (booklet) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Swiss National Museum, Zurich, Switzerland (booklet) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Zurich, Switzerland (booklet) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Restaurant Palmhof, Switzerland (menu) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Travel Tips, Switzerland (guide) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - All about Switzerland (guide) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - The best way to see Switzerland (guide) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Extrait de l'abc de la cuisine, Switzerland (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Taiwan coach tours (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - South Taiwan Republic of China (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Guide for Taiwan sightseeing (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Bangkok, Thailand (postcards) (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Travel, general: What to know before you go (pamphlet) 1960 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Travel, general: Travelers advantage (periodical) 2004 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Travel, general: How to create and coordinate your wardrobe for travel and other helpful travel tips (booklet) (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Travel, general: Gold preferred guest (brochure) (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Sultan Tours, Turkey (leaflet) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Istanbul area, Turkey (pamphlet) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Turkey Travel Guide (pamphlet) 1977 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Mugla (pamphlet) 1966 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Road Map of Turkey 1966 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Come to Turkey - Itineraries 1967 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Turkey Aegean Region 1967 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Turkey - Black Sea 1967 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Highway Map of Turkey 1972 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Turkey - region by region 1972 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Istanbul 1974 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Museum National History: Uruguay, Uruguay + Venezuela (18 publications) (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - S.S. Uruguay: Uruguay and Latin America (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Red Line Excursion: A Trip to Venezuela and Curacao (guide) 1889 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Caracas, Venezuela: This is Caracas To day [sic] (guide) (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Caracas, Venezuela: 12 aspectos de la nueva Caracas (postcards) (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Wales and Midlands: Esso Map (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - World (map) 1970 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - World (map) 1975 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - World portrait map (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Pocket Atlas of the World (map) (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - The Famous World Atlas 1941 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Cleartype General Map of the World on Mercator's Projection (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Postcards: Hotels, motels, restaurants, ships, World (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - The Mystic Oracle answers questions by wireless 1923 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - The Date Finder 1909 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - View of New York (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - View of San Francisco (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Views of London (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Cook's Vacation Tours 1914 (Box 8, Folder 4)